# PHILIPP WINSTON

# INTERNAL SALES REPRESENTATIVE

## CONTACT

+1 832.540.0191

PhilippWinston@gmail.com

♠ Webster, Texas

# **EDUCATION**

CODING BOOTCAMP FOR FULL STACK DEVELOPEMENT Rice University/ Feb- Aug 2023 IN PROGRESS

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA Winston Academy/ June 2016

### SKILLS

### | Technical

HTML

JavaScript

CSS

JQuery

Bootstrap

Node.js

MySQL

MongoDB

Express.js

React.js

### SUMMARY

I am a young professional ready be a key component with **your company**. Having proper training from a credible institution has provided me with knowledge of Full Stack Development. 9 years of customer service experience has provided me with excellent communication skills, resourcefulness, and a positive attitude. By combining these skills, I hope to be an asset to your team so we can find a better way to do business.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

INTERNAL SALES REPRESENTATIVE

Nan Ya Plastics / April 2022-Present

- Provides point of contact and service for customers
- Organizes and inputs orders in the AS400 software
- Provides the production team with the necessary order information to fulfill orders properly and efficiently
- Ensures orders are completed in a timely and effective manner
- Files and maintains records for retention and future orders

## RETAIL SALES ASSOCIATE

REI Store #173 / August 2020-April 2023

- Greeted and engaged with customers
- Answered products questions and guide product selections
- Set up promotional signage and materials
- Process credit card and cash transactions
- Followed technical protocols when assembling gear
- Worked with team members to generate and maintain standard operating procedures

### FRONT OF HOUSE PARTNER

Central Market H-E-B / November 2019-August 2020 (Laid off due to Covid-19)

- Greeted and assisted customers
- Maintained a clean and efficient workspace
- Utilized the First In, First Out rule
- Used safe food handling practices
- Worked in a fast paced environment

# PHILIPP WINSTON

### INTERNAL SALES REPRESENTATIVE

### SKILLS

#### | Professional

Leadership

Communication

**Customer Service** 

Organization

Creativity

Collaboration skills

Computer Proficiency

Resourceful

Microsoft Office

Problem Sloving

### INTEREST

- | Travel
- | Camping
- I Homebrewing
- | Culinary Arts
- | Woodworking
- | Classical Arts

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# TASTING SPECIALIST / COOKING SCHOOL ASSISTANT Central Market H-E-B / February 2018-November 2019

- Ordered supplies when needed
- Prepared food samples and demos
- Researched cooking techniques
- Assisted lead chefs in food prep
- Directed students when questions arose
- Provided demonstrations for students
- Be knowledgeable about beer/wine pairings
- Acquired proper knowledge of Chem Star and Q-San cleaning products, PPE (Personal Protection Equipment), Food safety and Sanitation certificate guidelines and TABC

#### **FISHMONGER**

Central Market H-E-B / January 2017-February 2018

- Kept a tidy and organized space
- Served customer needs
- Utilized knowledge of edible sea life
- Educated on Chem Star and Q-San cleaning products, PPE, Food Safety and Sanitation certificate guidelines, OSHA guidelines, HACCP (Hazard Analysis of Critical Control Points), and company guidelines

### **CASHIER**

H-E-B / April 2014-December 2016

- Greeted and assisted customers
- Handled credit card and cash transactions
- Managed a till
- Acquired knowledge of TABC regulations for alcohol sales

### REFERENCES

MICHELLE BRYANT

SELENE BALLESTAS

Marketing Coordinator

Store Manager

Nan Ya Plastics

REI #173

E: Michelle.neumadoors@gmail.com

E: Sballes@rei.com T: 281.488.0083

T: 281.748.6445